Some crimes never let you go.
Backtrace is a crime, action, adventure film directed by Brian A. Miller.
The lone surviving thief of a violent armored car robbery is sprung from a
high security facility and administered an experimental drug.
Lucas, played by Ryan Guzman.
Sykes, played by Sylvester Stallone.
MacDonald, played by Matthew Modine.
Erin, played by Meadow Williams.
Franks, played by Christopher McDonald.
Carter, played by Colin Egglesfield.
Backtrace is a 2018 American action crime thriller film directed by Brian A.
Miller, and starring Sylvester Stallone, Matthew Modine and Ryan Guzman.
The film was released as video on demand and limited theatrical release by
Lionsgate Premiere on December 14, 2018 in the United States.
The film explores themes of prison, thief, armored
car robbery, experimental drug.
The tone is dark and intense.